I see people often say, why are there so many migrants that come to the United States?
Why can't they just stay in their country?
And it is because the United States is constantly destabilizing their countries for their own
gain.
Case in point, Honduras.
Now, I want to make it clear that the current coup happening in Venezuela is also because
of the United States, and they are stating that it is because they want to stop the trafficking
of drugs.
However, in Honduras, their president, democratically elected Xiomara Castro de Zelaya,
just put this out last night.
To the Honduran people, I report with historical responsibility that based on verified intelligence
information, Juan Orlando Hernandez, pardoned in the U.S., plans his entry into the country
to proclaim the winner of the elections at the same time that an aggression is underway
aimed at breaking the constitutional and democratic order through a coup against my government.
So let me tell you about this man, Juan Orlando.
Juan Orlando Hernandez, the ex-president, was convicted last year for 45 years in federal
prison in the United States for drug trafficking and charged with $8 million fines.
Now, anybody who knows anything about when folks go into the feds, they know that most
folks do not come out of the feds unless they make a deal with the feds.
So, surprise, surprise, this man was pardoned by Donald Trump and is on his way back to Honduras?
Xiomara goes on to say,
In the face of this serious situation, I urgently request the conscious and peaceful support
of the Honduran people.
I call upon the people, social movements, collectives, grassroots organizations, militants, and citizens
to urgently and peacefully gather in Tegucigalpa to defend the popular mandate, reject any coup
attempt, and make visible to the world that a new coup is being hatched here.
This sounds like when people do those posts where they're like,
What you should not do is this, and you definitely shouldn't do this,
and you should absolutely do not do this, when they absolutely want you to do that.
Because, baby, what she's saying is,
Hey, I need y'all to pull up.
Anduda!
Squatter!
Because these people are trying to take over and don't let them.
Do not let them take over you either, United States-ians.
They're telling you that there should be a coup in Venezuela because of drug trafficking,
all while pardoning a convicted drug trafficker to return back to his home.
They are simultaneously deporting people who are not criminals
and stating that it is because they want to keep crime away from the United States
while literally freeing a convicted criminal in the United States.
Make it make sense.
It doesn't.
And if you're saying, Why does any of this matter?
Because it all comes back to your safety and to your well-being.
Well, and also because we just don't want people being harmed for no reason
because of U.S. intervention.
But I know some of y'all don't care about shit like that.
You know, like humanity and whatnot.
Support a real one.